https://waldenenvironmentalengineering.com/privacy-policy/

At Walden Environmental Engineering, we take your privacy
seriously. This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use
and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of the Site.
Information
Collection and Use
While using our site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally, identifiable information may include but is not limited to, your name (“Personal Information”) and email address.
Communications
We may use your personal information to contact you with
newsletters, marketing messages or promotional materials and other information
that you may find interesting. If you would prefer not to receive these
communications, you may unsubscribe from our list at any time by clicking on
the Unsubscribe link on our marketing emails or calling us at (516) 373-7618.
Log Data
Like many site operators, we collect information that your
browser sends whenever you visit our site (“log data”).
This log data may include information such as your
computer’s internet protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser
version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit,
the time spent on those pages and other statistics.
In addition, we may use third party services such as Google
Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this data in aggregate.
Cookies
Cookies are files that contain small amounts of data. They are sent from our website and stored on your computer’s hard drive. They may include an anonymous unique identifier.
Walden Environmental Engineering may use cookies in the
following ways:
1. To personalize the site. Walden Environmental Engineering may use cookies to personalize your experience on our website by displaying content Walden Environmental Engineering believes might interest you based on your information.
2. To estimate
the size of our audience. Each browser accessing the site is given a unique
cookie which is then used to determine the size of our audience and the extent
of repeat usage.
3. To track
visitor trends and patterns. We use the information provided by cookies to
improve, update and revise the features offered by Walden Environmental
Engineering. This, we believe, will provide our visitors with more useful
content and services.
You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to
indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies,
you may not be able to use some portions of our site.
Sharing of Personal Information
Walden Environmental Engineering does not share your
collected information with third parties.
Security
We make every reasonable effort to keep your information
secure. But remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or
method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use
commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot
guarantee its absolute security.
Changes to this
Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any
time. If and when we make changes to this policy, we will display a notice on
our website. By continuing to use the website after the notice has been
published constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please
contact us at (516) 373-7618.
Privacy Policy
© 2020 Walden. All Rights Reserved. Phone (516) 373-7618
Privacy Policy
